bmi-calculator.net 2017-02-23

# Privacy Policy

We are glad of your interest in BMI Calculator. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

For each visitor to our Web Page, our Web Server automatically logs statistical information such as the user's IP address, browser type, and the site where the user came from. None of this information can be used to personally identify an individual user. The information stored on our server may be used to provide statistics about the usage of this site, for the purpose of improving this site and to provide statistical information to advertisers. Only aggregated information is given, and the log file itself is not available to the public.

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. An advertiser may also display an advertisement that contains a cookie. These cookies are not sent from our site and we have no access to the information in these cookies.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our website and other sites on the internet. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

This site contains links to other sites. BMI Calculator is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you feel this site is not following its stated privacy policy or if you have any further questions, you may contact us at info_at_bmi-calculator.net ( replace _at_ with @ )

| Resources  
---  
Disclaimer  
Underweight Treatment  
Overweight Treatment  
Obesity Treatment  
  
| Calculators  
---  
BMI Calculator  
BMR Calculator  
Body Fat Calculator  
Waist to Hip Ratio Calculator  
Ideal Weight Calculator  
Weight Loss Calculator  
More Calculators
